<conversations>
  <conversation name="intro speech" speaker="archdemon">
    <line insertHeroName="true">Ah excellent. Welcome {{hero}}!</line>    
    <line>Long have we been at war with the humans. My soothsayers tell me that their legendary hero has appeared.</line>
    <line>I have called you from the void for one purpose.</line>
    <line>Dispose of this wretched hero and conquer the realm of mankind. Their existence is a blight on this otherwise pristine world.</line>
    <line>Now go!</line>
  </conversation>
	<conversation name="archdemon" speaker="archdemon">
		<line>Welcome back! I hope the war goes well.</line>
    <line>Crush those tiny humans into dust!</line>
	</conversation>
  <conversation name="save point description" speaker="imp">
    <line>This thing here is a void imprinter. Stepping on it will store your consciousness in the void should you ever need to leave this plane and return later.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="charlock war training" speaker="imp">
    <line>I'm training these layabouts for our assault on Rimuldar to the west.</line>    
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="charlock trainee 1" speaker="tiger">
    <line>All abilities effect the amount of elemental energy in the area. You can use the energy with Finishers. There's so much to learn.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="charlock trainee 2" speaker="tiger">
    <line>Finishers consume the elemental energy on battlefield. If there isn't enough energy on the battlefield when you try to use it, you will have wasted an oppurtunity.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="charlock trainee 3" speaker="tiger">
    <line>Thanks to the dark power of Archdemon Charon, your wounds will close completely after each battle; but that doesn't mean you will return to life.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="charlock throne skeleton" speaker="skeleton">
    <line>The soothsayers say that the island kingdom of Baron is where the hero was born.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="charlock throne ghost" speaker="ghost">
    <line>Somewhere in this world lie shrines to each of the elements: Fire, Water, Light, Dark, and Martial.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="archdemon personal guard" speaker="devilguard">
    <line>At long last we shall we reveal our true power to the humans. At long last we shall have our revenge!</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="stairs devilguard" speaker="devilguard">
    <line>Long live Archdemon Charon!</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="ghost charlock throne" speaker="ghost">
    <line>This castle used to belong to an ancient human kingdom until we monsters ousted them.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="skeleton charlock east wing" speaker="skeleton">
    <line>Ever wonder why the humans around here are so weak? As you venture farther afield the humans become more hardy as we haven't managed to spread that far yet.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="tiger charlock west wing" speaker="tiger">
    <line>The hero and his allies will be searching for the four pieces of legendary equipment said to have belonged to the ancient king Roto.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="charlock entrance guard" speaker="devilguard">
    <line>Just across the great river lies the heart of the human kingdom, Westmere.</line>    
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="golem joins" speaker="golem">q
    <line>**Rumble**  Together we can rid this world of the hero!  **Rumble**</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="Rimuldar Villager 1 Prefight">
    <line>Have at thee!</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="Rimuldar Villager 2 Prefight">
    <line>Why can't you monsters just leave us be?!</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="Rimuldar Merchant Prefight">
    <line>Leave! Leave our profits alone!</line>
    <line>Gyaaaah!</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="rimuldar general intro" speaker="general">
    <line>How dare you come into this town and try to kill us all!</line>
    <line>I am General Leo and you and your kind have seen the last of your days!</line>
    <line>Have at thee!</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="ghost joins" speaker="ghost">
    <line>Remember me? You killed me back in Rimuldar. Don't worry I'm not out for revenge. Lord Charon has returned me to this existence so that I can assist you.</line>
    <line>Together we can destroy the humans and bring honor to the Archdemon.</line>
  </conversation>
  <conversation name="kol golem guardian">
    <line>**Rumble**  We'll hold off any human resistance here.  **Rumble**</line>
    <line>**Rumble**  Go sack the town of Rimuldar to the south.  **Rumble**</line>
  </conversation>
  
  <!-- DEMO CONVERSATIONS -->
  <conversation name="demo king of baron">
    <line>I congratulate you on making it this far!</line>
    <line>Unfortunately the hero you've been searching for has already come and gone.</line>
    <line>He has the legendary sword, Tizon, and with it he will end your filthy line!</line>
    <line>Alas, you will not be around to see that come to pass.</line>
    <line>Have at thee!</line>
  </conversation>
</conversations>